# Tran Nhu Hai

HARDWARE ENGINEER
4 YEARS OF EXPERIENCE



#### **DETAILS**

Birthday: 30 July 1997

Gender: Male

Mail: trannhuhai.300797@gmail.com

Phone : 0383192637

Address: Nam Du Street, Linh Nam Ward, Hoang Mai District, Ha Noi City.

#### **INTRODUCE**

I have been working in the electrical and electronic field since 2019, with 4 years of experience as a technical staff in the following jobs: design PCB electronic circuit; embedded programming C/C++ with Arduino, STM8, STM32, AVR; testing the operation of electronic components (sensors, modules, etc); participating in the production of electronic circuits (soldering, assembling, testing the operation of PCB circuits, etc). With my working experience, I wish to participate and contribute my efforts to the company as a technical staff in designing PCB electronic circuits.

#### **EDUCATION**

> 2015 - July 2019

### HANOI UNIVERSITY OF INDUSTRY (HaUI)

Mode of study: Full-time

Major: Electrical and Electronic Engineering Technology

Degree classification: Good

#### **SKILLS**

#### Professional skill:

- Design hardware for electronic circuits, using Altium Designer software tool. Other skills:
  - Read mechanical drawings, using SOLIDWORKS software tool.
  - Able to make PCB sample circuits, test circuits.
  - Welding electronic components, assembling, checking operation, good fault finding with PCB electronic circuits.
  - Basic programming: C/C++ (Arduino, STM8, STM32, AVR).
  - Good using: Word, Excel, Google Sheet, etc.
  - English language: read, write.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### > 2019 - Sep 2022

#### SMD ELECTRONIC JOINT STOCK COMPANY

Address: No. 01, Nguyen Xa 1 residential group, Minh Khai Ward, Bac Tu Liem District, Ha Noi City.

#### Technical staff

- Designed simple electronic circuits. Made circuits for test. Wrote programs to test some sensors, modules, LCD displays, etc.
- Electronic circuit manufacturing: Soldered components. Loaded code. Tested and repaired large quantities of electronic circuits.
- Designed some products of filter, sound electronic circuit, fan control circuit.

#### Oct 2022 - Jan 2024

#### VNM SIMULATION EQUIPMENT JOINT STOCK COMPANY

Address: No. 55 - Binh Doan Region 12, Dai Mo Street, Dai Mo Ward, Nam Tu Liem District, Ha Noi City.

#### Technical staff

- Designed PCB electronic circuits for some new products.
- Upgraded PCB electronic circuits for some available products.
- Made sample circuits, checked the operation of the designed PCBs.
- Analysed causes and repaired circuit errors.
- Exported BOM and support files for PCB electronic circuit production.
- Checked components in stock. Found and compared necessary components from suppliers.
- Completed PCB electronic circuit design for some products:
  - VNM Motion Controller the motion simulation control product uses servo drives. It reads the game control signals from the PC computer and outputs the servo motor control signals.
  - VNM GT Steering Wheel V1, VNM Button Box V1, VNM SEQ Shifter V2 The products that read, receive control signals and put them into game
    applications on PC computer. The product is designed like a racing car.

#### CAREER OBJECTIVE

- Continuously learn from experience in product design and work.

## Some pictures of Schematic and PCB are designed:

https://github.com/trannhuhai-300797/storage.picture.designed-PCB